# Sunny Bansidhar Pandey

Full-Stack Developer

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3+ years of related experience.

 $\times$ 

pandeysunny01@gmail.com

8668816974

Mumbai, India

https://sunny-port-folio.vercel.app

## **Work Experience**

#### **Alphaspec Consulting LLP**

#### **Full-Stack Developer (Java)**

04/2021 - 05/2023

Personalized IT Consulting Service based Achievements/Tasks.

- Documented module specification.
- Prepared design specification including UML diagram for the front-end layer.
- Designed and implemented the application in layered architecture presentation, service and data.
- Exposed and fixed essential application problems like optimization, concurrency, web security XSS, Business logic bugs.
- Implemented JWT for token-based authentication.
- Created a RESTFull client component that pulls JSON data with the help of Apache camel directly to the DB.
- Integrated AWS S3 for file upload from client and Apache camel for file upload to local and for Event mail triggering.
- Created the custom tag for user restricted page controls. Using JPA for CRUD operation from DB to java objects.

## **Bahwan Cybertek**

#### **Software Developer (Java)**

05/2023 - Present

Developer of IT-related software products designed to offer digital transformation services.

- Designed and developed the whole application for client (MahaIT).
- Work with internal teams to develop a quality product/application.
- Implemented the application in layered architecture.
- Fixed essential application problems like concurrency, web security, Business logic bugs, etc.
- Quickly adapted old technologies to work on old tech applications.
- Added new features/functionality and even improved the performance of old ones.
- Provided suggestions to the juniors and even to seniors.

## **Education**

#### **Masters in Computer Application (MCA)**

Mumbai University

05/2017 - 05/2020 CGPA - 5.21

**Bachelors of Commerce (B.com)** 

Mumbai University

06/2013 - 06/2016 CGPA - 5.2

# Skills

Java Spring Spring Boot JPA Hibernate MySql OracleDB MongoDB Angular 12+ ReactJs(Intermediate)

HTML5

CSS

Javascript

JQuerv

Bootstrac

Tailwind CSS (Intermediate)

## **Projects**

- All projects can be found here -> https://github.com/sunny12121
- Basic projects -
  - Birthday celebration (static website)
    - Made in HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap.
  - File converter
    - Made in Java, Spring boot, Thymeleaf, HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap and other extensions for PDF, Doc convertion, etc.
  - Portfolio
    - Made in ReactJs, Tailwind CSS.
  - Library management system
    - Made in Java, Spring boot, MariaDB, Angular 12, Bootstrap.

#### **Achievements**

Managed team of 3 developers

Guided and provided them with the solution as and when needed.

Maintained and handled Projects of PHP parallely with Java.

Projects like RAK Ceramics and Keihin Fie (Hitachi Astemo FIE Pvt. Ltd.)

- Designed, developed and leaded a project solely.

Handled project named DSP portal.

Handled and provided support for 2 projects in a day

Projects like SARA and LICHFL.

# Languages

- English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

- Marathi

Professional Working Proficiency